Guide to the Stanford Channel Master Videorecordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Videos (Box 1)
  - Issues and Ideas
    - My Cultures, My Selves, 96-433 (Box 49)
    - No Man's Land, 96-434 (Box 49)
    - Latina Immigrants: East and West Coast Experiences, 97-435 (Box 49)
    - U.S.- Russia Relations, 97-436 (Box 49)
    - Lesbian and Gay Rights: Organizing for Change, 97-437 (Box 49)
    - Economic Policy Making and the Making of "Choiceless Democracies", 97-438 (Box 49)
    - Is Teaching in Women's Studies a Political Act?, 97-439 (Box 49)
    - Owning Free Speech, 97-440 (Box 49)
    - Homosexuality: Lifestyle Choice or Sexual Condition?, 97-441 (Box 49)
    - Queer Histories: Margery Kempe, Robert Gluck and the 104th Congress, 97-442 (Box 50)
    - The Ethics of Analogy: Critical Discourse on Race and Sexuality, 97-444 (Box 50)
    - Cracks in the Iron Closet: Travels in Gay and Lesbian Russia, 97-445 (Box 50)
    - Too Sexy for Our Suits: Recent Trends in Sexual Harrassment Law, 97-446 (Box 50)
    - Reflections on Student Activism, 1960s to 1990s, 97-447 (Box 50)
    - Loose Nukes: Security Issues on the U.S.- Russia Agenda, 97-448 (Box 50)
    - The Political Integration of Racial and Ethnic Minorities, 97-449 (Box 50)
    - The Society of Otherness and the Otherness of Society: Community, Identity and the Philosophy of Gay Rights, 97-450 (Box 50)
    - Ooga-Booga Journalism: Africa in the Western Media, 97-451 (Box 50)
    - Trusting the American Jury, 97-452 (Box 50)
    - The White Negress and the Heavy Duty Dike: On Sandra Bernhart's "Without You I'm Nothing", 97-443 (Box 50)
    - The Real Struggle for Political Power in America, 97-453 (Box 51)
    - Federal Regulators' Biotechnology Follies, 97-454 (Box 51)
    - Governing the Modern University: Is It Even Worth Trying?, 97-455 (Box 51)
    - "Shut Up You Liar!" The Decline of Civility in the U.S. Congress, 97-456 (Box 51)
    - Publishing Gossip, 97-457 (Box 51)
    - Digital Marketing, 97-458 (Box 51)
    - Are Professional Sports Teams Worth It?, 97-459 (Box 51)
    - The Future of the Internet, 97-460 (Box 51)
    - Gridlock in Washington, 97-461 (Box 51)
    - Manufacturing and Humanity, 97-462 (Box 51)
    - Psychological Perspectives on Fairness in Public Policy, 97-463 (Box 51)
    - Telecommunications Competition: Past, Present and Future, 97-464 (Box 52)
    - The Press 25 Years After Watergate, 97-465 (Box 52)
    - Elite Institutions in a Democratic Society, 97-466 (Box 52)
    - Children in War, 97-467 (Box 52)
    - Music, Technology and Humanity, 97-468 (Box 52)
    - Thoughts for New Century, Program #1: America's Role in the World, 97-469 (Box 52)
    - Chinese Economic Growth: Past, Present and Future, 97-470 (Box 52)
    - America's Unethical Health Care Delivery System Mirrors America's Unethical Society, 98-401 (Box 52)
    - Germs as Arms: What Progress to Control?, 98-471 (Box 52)
    - Thoughts for A New Century, Program #2: America's Role in the World, 98-472 (Box 52)
    - Relationships Between Men and Women in the Inner City, 98-473 (Box 52)
    - U.S. Policy and an Expanding NATO, 98-474 (Box 52)
    - Derivatives and Financial Innovation, 98-475 (Box 53)
    - Natural Capitalism, 98-476 (Box 53)
    - Health Reform and Health Care Costs: A Global Perspective, 98-477 (Box 53)
    - Thoughts for a New Century, Program #3: America's Role in the World, 98-478 (Box 53)
    - From "Making Babies for the Revolution" to Planned Parenthood: The Metamorphosis of the Female Black Panther Party Revolutionary, 1967 - 1982, 98-479 (Box 53)
    - Thoughts for a New Century, Program #4: Writing a New American Narrative, 98-480 (Box 53)
    - Assessing the Cost of the Millenium Bug, 98-481 (Box 53)
    - Breaking the News: How the Media Undermine American Democracy, 98-482 (Box 53)
    - America's New Religious Landscape: Negotiating Identities, Negotiating Differences, 98-483 (Box 53)
    - A Life in Basketball: Before and After Title IX, 98-484 (Box 53)
    - The Bosnia Imbroglio: No War No Peace, 98-485 (Box 53)
    - Europe and the Euro, 98-486 (Box 54)
    - Choices for Retirement Savings, 98-487 (Box 54)
    - Publishing and the Law, 98-488 (Box 54)
    - Renegade Publishing, 98-489 (Box 54)
    - Rules for Revolutionaries, 98-490 (Box 54)
    - Competing on the Edge: Structured Chaos, 98-491 (Box 54)
    - Present Danger: Weapons of Mass Destruction, 98-492 (Box 54)
    - Will Social Security Reform Ever Happen?, 98-494 (Box 54)
    - Don't Ask, Don't Tell: Is It Working?, 98-495 (Box 54)
    - The Future of Capital Real Estate Markets, 98-496 (Box 54)
    - California's Children: Language Issues for the Next Millenium, 98-497 (Box 55)
    - Measuring Up: Standards, Assessment and School Reform, 98-498 (Box 55)
    - U.S. vs. Microsoft, 98-499 (Box 55)
    - Democracy and the Internet, 99-400 (Box 55)
    - Perspectives on Clinton's Race Initiative, 99-402 (Box 55)
    - Will the Media be the End of Us?, 99-403 (Box 55)
    - Race and Adoption, 99-404 (Box 55)
    - Latin American Economies After the Asian Crisis, 99-405 (Box 55)
    - Can the Press Fix Itself?, 99-406 (Box 55)
    - The Interaction of Economics and Security, 99-407 (Box 55)
    - International Business: Global Challenges, 99-408 (Box 55)
    - Immigrants in the Labor Market, 99-409 (Box 56)
    - Fresh Water in the New Century: Old Problems, New Solutions?, 99-410 (Box 56)
    - Global Telecommunications: An Update, 99-411 (Box 56)
    - Older Mothers and Adult Daughters, 99-412 (Box 56)
    - The Global Economy: China, Europe, India, Japan and Latin America, 99-413 (Box 56)
    - The U.S. Economy: Where Do We Go From Here?, 99-414 (Box 56)
    - Language and Ethnicity: Minority and Majority Perspectives, 99-415 (Box 56)
    - The Terrorist Threat to American Security, 99-416 (Box 56)
    - Future of the Internet, 99-417/a (Box 56)
    - Advances and Challenges in Internet Design, 99-417/b (Box 56)
    - Japan's Economic Crisis 1990-1999: From Superpower to Has-Been?, 99-418 (Box 56)
    - High Tech: Market Competition and Political Risk, 99-419 (Box 57)
    - Media Meltdown: An Examination of the Scandalous Press, 99-420 (Box 57)
    - Working With Couples During Two Family Transitions: Effects on Marriage, Parenting, and Their Children's Adjustment, 99-421 (Box 57)
    - Desert Storm or Thyroid Storm? An Inquiry, 99-422 (Box 57)
    - Academic Publishing in an Increasing Competitive Environment, 99-423 (Box 57)
    - Fighting Back: Eradicating Violence Against Our Community, 99-424 (Box 57)
    - Silicon Valley 101, 99-425 (Box 57)
    - Frontiers in Conservation: The Changing Face of Environmental Protection, 99-426 (Box 57)
    - When the Exotic Becomes Erotic: Explaining the Enigma of Sexual Orientation, 99-427 (Box 57)
    - Visual Information: All About Hands, 99-428 (Box 57)
    - Web Publishing: Lessons Learned, 99-429 (Box 58)
    - Investing in India: What Are the Prospects?, 99-430 (Box 58)
    - Insights on Innovation, 99-431 (Box 58)
    - The New E-Business, 99-432 (Box 58)
    - Magazines Around the World, 99-433 (Box 58)
    - The Hollywood Connection: A Conversation with David Brown, 99-434 (Box 58)
    - After Columbine: School Violence, 99-435 (Box 58)
    - Economic Policy Reform in Brazil, 99-436 (Box 58)
    - A Unified Theory of Asset Market Volatility, 99-437 (Box 58)
    - High Tech Ties: Taiwan and Silicon Valley, 99-439 (Box 58)
    - A Discussion of Medicare Reform, 99-438 (Box 58)
    - GSB Q&A with Jeff Bezos, 00-440 (Box 59)
    - GSB Q&A with Steve Ballmer, 00-441 (Box 59)
    - The Global Economy in the New Millenium, 00-442 (Box 59)
    - Politics and Economics, 00-443 (Box 59)
    - Economic Reporting with Marshall Loeb, 00-444 (Box 59)
    - GSB Q&A with Scott McNealy, 00-445 (Box 59)
    - Why Aging Is a Feminist Issue, 00-446 (Box 59)
    - 2000 De Leeuw Lecture: Election Year; but do we really elect whom we want?, 00-447 (Box 59)
    - Politics, Policy and Reality: What's Really Going on in Washington?, 00-448 (Box 59)
    - Transforming America: the Role of the Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual and Transgender Community, 00-449 (Box 59)
    - Should San Francisco Adopt a Living Wage Initiative?, 00-450 (Box 59)
    - An Economic Perspective on E-Commerce, 00-451 (Box 60)
    - Is Demography Destiny, 00-452 (Box 60)
    - A Status Report: Indian Economic Policy Reform, 00-453 (Box 60)
    - E-Publishing in the New Millennium, 00-454 (Box 60)
    - LIFE: Our Century in Pictures and the Power of Photographs, 00-455 (Box 60)
    - The Microsoft Case: Implications for Competition and Innovation, 00-456 (Box 60)
    - The Presidential Candidates' Social Security Plans, 00-457 (Box 60)
    - Making Peace in Northern Ireland, 00-458 (Box 60)
    - The Fountain of Age, 00-459 (Box 60)
    - Philanthropy in Silicon Valley, 00-460 (Box 60)
    - China's Population: Prospects and Problems, 00-461 (Box 60)
    - Building HIV/AIDS Awareness in Africa, 00-462 (Box 61)
    - Aging and the Media, 00-463 (Box 61)
    - Achieving Self-Renewal, 00-464 (Box 61)
    - Principles of Internet Marketing, 00-465 (Box 61)
    - What's Possible in Washington in the Next Four Years ?, 01-468 (Box 61)
    - Management and Control of Wild Elephant Populations, 01-469 (Box 61)
    - Census 2000: A Demographic Turning Point for the Nation?, 01-470 (Box 61)
    - Election 2000: Epilogue, 01-471 (Box 61)
    - The Internet and the Economy, 01-472 (Box 61)
    - Population-Health Issues and Global Warming, 01-466 (Box 61)
    - Incentives and the Endangered Species Act, 01-467 (Box 61)
    - The Future of the Internet, E-Commerce, and Public Policy #1, 01-473/a (Box 62)
    - The Future of the Internet, E-Commerce and Public Policy #2, 01-473/b (Box 62)
    - The Future of the Internet, E-Commerce and Public Policy #3, 01-473/c (Box 62)
    - The Future of the Internet, E-Commerce, and Public Policy #4, 01-473/d (Box 62)
    - The Future of the Internet, E-Commerce, and Public Policy #5, 01-473/e (Box 62)
    - Is the Competitive Electricity Market Possible in California?, 01-475 (Box 62)
    - Population Aging and Oldest Old in China, 01-476 (Box 62)
    - Difficult Dialogues: Aging in the 21st Century, 01-474/a (Box 62)
    - Difficult Dialogues: Aging in the 21st Century, 01-474/b (Box 62)
    - Difficult Dialogues: Aging in the 21st Century, 01-474/c (Box 62)
    - The Wealth Effect: Asset Price Movements and the Real Economy, 01-479 (Box 63)
    - A Pigment of Your Imagination, 01-477 (Box 63)
    - Linguistic Profiling in America's Courts, Schools and Society, 01-478 (Box 63)
    - 2001 Knight Lecture: Rewriting the Future: Journalism and the Internet, 01-480 (Box 63)
    - Race and Ethnicity in Early 21st Century America, 01-481 (Box 63)
    - The Bush Agenda: Prospects for Tax Cuts and Social Security Reform, 01-482 (Box 63)
    - Reforming the International Financial Institutions, 01-483 (Box 63)
    - Fractured Social Bodies: The Power of Oral History and the Case of India's Partition, 01-484 (Box 63)
    - The IMF's Role in Stabilizing the World Economy, 01-485 (Box 63)
    - 13th Boething Lecture on Forests and the Human Predicament: Negotiating Nature: Saving Urban Forests, 01-486 (Box 63)
    - Building an Effective Statewide Progressive Alliance that Incorporates the needs of African Americans: How do Blacks thrive in the midst of the changing demographic realities of California?, 01-487 (Box 63)
  - QuadrAngles
    - Years of Hope, Days of Rage: Stanford in the 1960s, 95-501 (Box 64)
    - Stanford: A Sentimental Journey, 95-502 (Box 64)
    - Champions: A Century of Stanford Sports, 95-503 (Box 64)
    - Building a Multi-Cultural Curriculum, 95-504 (Box 64)
    - Grand Design: A History of the Stanford Museum and Experiencing Stanford, 95-505 (Box 64)
    - Great Moments of the Big Game, 95-506 (Box 64)
    - Rosebowl Highlights 1971 & 1972 / A Pint of Life, 95-507 (Box 64)
    - Stanford's Damaged Treasure: Frank Lloyd Wright's Hanna House, 96-508 (Box 64)
    - Stanford Builds for the 21st Century, 96-510 (Box 64)
    - Making a Difference: Stories from the Field, 96-511 (Box 64)
    - Exploring Inter-Disciplinary Studies at Stanford, 96-512 (Box 64)
    - Stanford at the Sun Bowl, 97-513 (Box 64)
    - Service Opportunities at Stanford, 00-517 (Box 65)
    - Research at SLAC: An Overview, 01-518 (Box 65)
    - English at Stanford, 1891-2000, 01-519 (Box 65)
    - Bill Hewlett and Graduate Student Life in Fred Terman's Lab, 01-520 (Box 65)
    - Connecting the Generations: Celebrating the African-American Experience at Stanford, 97-514 (Box 65)
    - Innovation in Teaching and Learning at Stanford, 98-515 (Box 65)
    - Mrs. Hoover's "Pueblo Walls": What Kind of Architecture is the Lou Henry Hoover House?, 99-516 (Box 65)
  - Continuing Studies Program
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #1, 95-601/a (Box 65)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #1, 95-601/b (Box 65)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #2, 95-602/a (Box 65)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #2, 95-602/b (Box 65)
    - The War on Drugs: History, Policy and Alternatives - Program #4, 96-614 (Box 67)
    - The War on Drugs: History, Policy and Alternatives - Program #5, 96-615 (Box 67)
    - The War on Drugs: History, Policy and Alternatives - Program #6, 96-616 (Box 67)
    - The War on Drugs: History, Policy and Alternatives - Program #7, 96-617 (Box 67)
    - The War on Drugs: History, Policy and Alternatives - Program #8, 96-618 (Box 67)
    - The War on Drugs: History, Policy and Alternatives - Program #9, 96-619 (Box 67)
    - The War on Drugs: History, Policy and Alternatives - Program #10, 96-620 (Box 67)
    - Gothic Cathedrals and the Great Churches of England, 1150-1350, Program #1, 96-621 (Box 67)
    - Gothic Cathedrals and the Great Churches of England, 1150-1350, Program#2, 96-622 (Box 67)
    - Gothic Cathedrals and the Great Churches of England, 1150-1350, Program #3, 96-623 (Box 67)
    - Gothic Cathedrals and the Great Churches of England, 1150-1350, Program #4, 96-624 (Box 67)
    - Gothic Cathedrals and Great Churches of England, 1150-1350, Program #5, 96-625 (Box 68)
    - Gothic Cathedrals and Great Churches of England, 1150-1350, Program #6, 96-626 (Box 68)
    - Gothic Cathedrals and the Great Churches of England, 1150-1350, Program#7, 96-627 (Box 68)
    - Gothic Cathedrals and the Great Churches of England, 1150-1350, Program #8, 96-628 (Box 68)
    - Gothic Cathedrals and the Great Churches of England, 1150-1350, Program #9, 96-629 (Box 68)
    - Gothic Cathedrals and the Great Churches of England, 1150-1350, Program #10, 96-630 (Box 68)
    - The Brain: An Owner's Manual, Program #1, 96-631 (Box 68)
    - The Brain: An Owner's Manual, Program #2, 96-632 (Box 68)
    - The Brain: An Owner's Manual, Program #3, 96-633 (Box 68)
    - The Brain: An Owner's Manual, Program #4, 96-634 (Box 68)
    - The Brain: An Owner's Manual, Program #5, 96-635 (Box 68)
    - The Brain: An Owner's Manual, Program #6, 96-636 (Box 69)
    - The Brain: An Owner's Manual, Program #7, 96-637 (Box 69)
    - The Brain: An Owner's Manual, Program #8, 96-638 (Box 69)
    - The Brain: An Owner's Manual, Program #9, 96-639 (Box 69)
    - The Brain: An Owner's Manual, Program #10, 96-640 (Box 69)
    - Why Read It? 'Old' and 'New' Classics, Part 1, 97-641 (Box 69)
    - Why Read It? 'Old' and 'New' Classics, Part 2, 97-642 (Box 69)
    - Why Read It? 'Old' and 'New' Classics, Part 3, 97-643 (Box 69)
    - Why Read It? 'Old' and 'New' Classics, Part 4, 97-644 (Box 69)
    - Why Read It? 'Old' and 'New' Classics, Part 5, 97-645 (Box 70)
    - Why Read It? 'Old' and 'New' Classics, Part 6, 97-646 (Box 70)
    - Why Read It? 'Old' and 'New' Classics, Part 7, 97-647 (Box 70)
    - Why Read It? 'Old' and 'New' Classics, Part 8, 97-648 (Box 70)
    - Why Read It? 'Old' and 'New' Classics, Part 9, 97-649 (Box 70)
    - Why Read It? 'Old' and 'New' Classics, Part 10, 97-650 (Box 70)
    - Transatlantic Modernism: Paris and New York in the Early 20th Century, 97-651 (Box 70)
    - Darwin, Evolution and Galapagos, Program #3, 97-663 (Box 72)
    - Darwin, Evolution and Galapagos, Program #4, 97-664 (Box 72)
    - Darwin, Evolution and Galapagos, Program #5, 97-665 (Box 72)
    - Darwin, Evolution and Galapagos, Program #6 tape #1, 97-666 (Box 72)
    - Darwin, Evolution and Galapagos, Program #6, 97-666 (Box 72)
    - Darwin, Evolution and Galapagos, Program #7 tape #1, 97-667 (Box 72)
    - Darwin, Evolution and Galapagos, Program #7, 97-667 (Box 72)
    - Darwin, Evolution and Galapagos, Program #8, 97-668 (Box 72)
    - Darwin, Evolution and Galapagos, Program #9, 97-669 (Box 72)
    - Darwin, Evolution and Galapagos, Program #10 tape #1, 97-670 (Box 72)
    - Darwin, Evolution and Galapagos, Program #10, 97-670 (Box 72)
    - Molecular Tools: How to Manipulate DNA and Proteins AND Microarrays: Laboratories on a Chip, 99-672 (Box 72)
    - Gene Mapping: How to Find Disease Genes and Pharmaceuticals: How to Find a New Drug, 99-673 (Box 72)
    - Life After 2000: Biotechnology and the Human Genome Project, 99-671 (Box 72)
    - Classical Archaeology: Experiences of the Discipline, 00-676 (Box 73)
    - The Times of Our Lives: On Living With and In Time, 00-679/a (Box 73)
    - The Times of Our Lives: On Living With and In Time, 00-679/b (Box 73)
    - The Times of Our Lives: On Living With and In Time tape #1, 00-679/c (Box 73)
    - The Times of Our Lives: On Living With and In Time tape #2, 00-679/c (Box 73)
    - Biotech Treatments: Gene Therapy, Tissue Engineering, etc. AND Bioinformatics: Computers Meet Sequences, 99-674 (Box 73)
    - When Genes Are Turned On: Expression Analysis Using Computers AND Social Issues of Genomics: What is Ethical? What is Legal?, 99-675 (Box 73)
    - From Digital Michelangelo to Robotic Surgery: Stanford's Computer Luminaries, 00-677 (Box 73)
    - From Digital Michelangelo to Robotic Surgery: Stanford's Computer Luminaries, 00-678 (Box 73)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #4, 95-604/a (Box 66/A)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #4, 95-604/b (Box 66/A)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #5, 95-605/a (Box 66/A)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #5, 95-605/b (Box 66/A)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #6, 95-606/a (Box 66/A)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #6, 95-606/b (Box 66/A)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #7, 95-607/a (Box 66/A)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #3, 95-603/a (Box 66/A)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #3, 95-603/b (Box 66/A)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #7, 95-607/b (Box 66/B)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #8, 95-608/a (Box 66/B)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #8, 95-608/b (Box 66/B)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #9, 95-609/a (Box 66/B)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #9, 95-609/b (Box 66/B)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #10, 95-610/a (Box 66/B)
    - Europe and America in the Modern Age, Kennedy/Sheehan Program #10, 95-610/b (Box 66/B)
    - The War on Drugs: History, Policy and Alternatives - Program #1 tape #1, 96-611 (Box 66/B)
    - The War on Drugs: History, Policy and Alternatives - Program #1 tape #2, 96-611 (Box 66/B)
    - The War on Drugs: History, Policy and Alternatives - Program #2 tape #1, 96-612 (Box 66/B)
    - The War on Drugs: History, Policy and Alternatives - Program #2 tape #2, 96-612 (Box 66/B)
    - The War on Drugs: History, Policy and Alternatives - Program #3 tape #1, 96-613 (Box 66/B)
    - The War on Drugs: History, Policy and Alternatives - Program #3 tape #2, 96-613 (Box 66/B)
    - Transatlantic Modernism: Paris and New York in the Early 20th Century, 97-652 (Box 71/A)
    - Transatlantic Modernism: Paris and New York in the Early 20th Century, 97-653 (Box 71/A)
    - Transatlantic Modernism: Paris and New York in the Early 20th Century, 97-654 (Box 71/A)
    - Transatlantic Modernism: Paris and New York in the Early 20th Century, 97-655 (Box 71/A)
    - Transatlantic Modernism: Paris and New York in the Early 20th Century, 97-656 (Box 71/A)
    - Transatlantic Modernism: Paris and New York in the Early 20th Century, 97-657 (Box 71/B)
    - Transatlantic Modernism: Paris and New York in the Early 20th Century, 97-658 (Box 71/B)
    - Transatlantic Modernism: Paris and New York in the Early 20th Century, 97-659 (Box 71/B)
    - Transatlantic Modernism: Paris and New York in the Early 20th Century, 97-660 (Box 71/B)
    - Darwin, Evolution and Galapagos, 97-661 (Box 71/B)
    - Darwin, Evolution and Galapagos, Program #2, 97-662 (Box 71/B)
  - InterChange
    - Interview with Claude Steele, 95-701 (Box 73)
    - Interview with Elizabeth Tallent, 95-702 (Box 73)
    - Interview with Sidney Drell, 95-703 (Box 73)
    - Interview with Arthur Kornberg, 95-704 (Box 74)
    - Interview with Philip Zimbardo, 95-705 (Box 74)
    - Interview with Condoleezza Rice, 95-706 (Box 74)
    - Interview with Martin Perl, 95-707 (Box 74)
    - Interview with Harry Elam, 95-708 (Box 74)
    - Interview with Gregory Freidin, 95-709 (Box 74)
    - Interview with Gerhard Casper, 95-710 (Box 74)
    - Interview with Elisabeth Pate-Cornell, 95-711 (Box 74)
    - Interview with Clayborne Carson, 96-712 (Box 74)
    - Interview with Terry Karl, 96-713 (Box 74)
    - Interview with Thomas Seligman, 96-714 (Box 74)
    - Interview with Laura Carstensen, 96-715 (Box 74)
    - Interview with Eugene Bauer, 96-716 (Box 75)
    - Interview with Craig Heller, 96-717 (Box 75)
    - Interview with Kathleen Sullivan, 96-718 (Box 75)
    - Interview with Deborah Gordon, 96-719 (Box 75)
    - Interview with Gordon Chang, 96-720 (Box 75)
    - Interview with Norman Naimark, 97-721 (Box 75)
    - Interview with Robert Warrior, 97-722 (Box 75)
    - Interview with Ernle Young, 97-723 (Box 75)
    - Interview with Estelle Freedman, 97-724 (Box 75)
    - Interview with Stephen Schneider, 97-725 (Box 75)
    - Interview with Coit Blacker, 97-726 (Box 75)
    - Interview with John Rickford, 97-727 (Box 76)
    - Interview with Douglas Osheroff, 97-728 (Box 76)
    - Interview with Jack Rakove, 97-729 (Box 76)
    - Interview with Donald Kennedy, 97-730 (Box 76)
    - Interview with Margaret Jane Radin, 97-731 (Box 76)
    - Interview with Leonore Herzenberg, 97-732 (Box 76)
    - Interview with John Hennessy, 97-733 (Box 76)
    - Interview with Daniel Okimoto, 97-734 (Box 76)
    - Interview with Lawrence Lau, 97-735 (Box 76)
    - Interview with Donald Roberts, 97-736 (Box 76)
    - Interview with Deborah Rhode, 97-737 (Box 76)
    - Interview with Bill Bradley, 98-738 (Box 77)
    - Interview with Anne Kiremidjian, 98-739 (Box 77)
    - Interview with Carl Djerassi, 98-740 (Box 77)
    - Interview with Eric Roberts, 98-741 (Box 77)
    - Interview with Steven Chu, 98-742 (Box 77)
    - Interview with William Damon, 98-743 (Box 77)
    - Interview with Miguel Mendez, 98-744 (Box 77)
    - Interview with Mike Montgomery, 98-745 (Box 77)
    - Interview with Diane Middlebrook, 98-746 (Box 77)
    - Interview with Frances Conley, 98-747 (Box 77)
    - Interview with Robert Gregg, 98-748 (Box 77)
    - Interview with Hazel Markus, 98-749 (Box 78)
    - Interview with Clayborne Carson, 98-750 (Box 78)
    - Interview with Margaret Neale, 99-751 (Box 78)
    - Interview with Elizabeth Bernhardt, 99-752 (Box 78)